<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>PyLadies</title><link>http://pyladi.es/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://pyladi.es/feeds/all.rss.xml" rel="self"></atom:link><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 15:12:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><item><title>PyCon Proposal Brainstorm Session August 27th</title><link>http://pyladi.es/2012/08/25/pycon_branstorm</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Ever thought about speaking? Want to give speaking at PyCon a shot, but not sure what to talk about? Even if you have a tiny inkling that you’d want to speak, beginner level or advanced, come to our &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.eventbrite.com/event/4207274070?ref=ebtnebregn"&gt;workshop&lt;/a&gt; to get help brainstorming ideas &amp;amp; learn what makes a good proposal!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join the PyLadies hangout, open to PyLadies and PyLaddies, with help from PyLadies’ leaders, previous years PyCon speakers &amp;amp; current Program Committee members (e.g. the folks that review proposals) to ideate, write, and submit your proposal to speak, give a tutorial, or a poster session at PyCon 2013.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Space is limited by the Google Hangout technology. An invite link will be sent out about 15 minutes prior to the start time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those in the Bay Area, be sure to check out the PyLadies San Francisco &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.meetup.com/PyLadiesSF/events/76870962/"&gt;meetup&lt;/a&gt;, Workshop: Talk Proposal Writing for PyCon, on Tuesday, August 28th.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Lynn Root</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2012 15:12:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>tag:pyladi.es,2012-08-25:2012/08/25/pycon_branstorm</guid></item><item><title>MOAR Womenz at DjangoConUS!</title><link>http://pyladi.es/2012/07/25/pyladies_at_djangocon</link><description>&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to go to &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://www.djangocon.us"&gt;DjangoCon 2012&lt;/a&gt; in Washington, D.C. — or know a talented developer who does — but cannot attend due to financial hardship, &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/viewform?formkey=dDc1X2hrUGJVRGdEWnRjTklxR2tSNFE6MQ#gid=0"&gt;please apply for financial aid&lt;/a&gt; through DjangoCon. And, if you’re a PyLady (as opposed to a PyLaddie), please indicate that you would like to be considered for a PyLadies grant on that form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year’s conference goes from Sept. 3 – Sept. 9. The deadline for the PyLadies grant submission is Friday, August 3rd.  We apologize for the short notice, but we know that people need time to make travel plans/request days off from work, etc.  You will hear from us by the end of the week after applications are submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you know of a talented, deserving female developer who might benefit greatly from attending DjangoCon, email &lt;a class="reference external" href="mailto:info&amp;#64;pyladies.com"&gt;info&amp;#64;pyladies.com&lt;/a&gt;.  We’ll do our best to help as many women as possible. Many thanks to the DjangoCon organizers and the Python Software Foundation for helping the PyLadies manage this program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal of this program is to bring new talent to the Djangosphere by supporting developers and giving them opportunity to make connections in the community. Your support of PyLadies’ outreach efforts will pay off hugely over the long term by improving the diversity of the industry as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Companies &amp;amp; Individuals are invited to offer funding for talented developers who have demonstrated or show potential for a serious commitment to diversity in the Django commnunity. Donations will go through the &lt;a class="reference external" href="http://python.org/psf"&gt;Python Software Foundation&lt;/a&gt;, and are thus tax-deductible, yeah!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please email &lt;a class="reference external" href="mailto:sponsors&amp;#64;pyladies.com"&gt;sponsors&amp;#64;pyladies.com&lt;/a&gt; if you’d like to send a woman developer to DjangoCon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Lynn Root</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2012 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>tag:pyladi.es,2012-07-25:2012/07/25/pyladies_at_djangocon</guid></item></channel></rss>